macroaxis.com 2019-12-25

# Macroaxis Privacy Policy Documents

  * About Us
  * Contact Us
  * Terms of Use
  * Settings

Our goal is to make Macroaxis the most trusted site in investment management. To do this, we need your help and any suggestions for improvement hits can be sent to us directly via our feedback form. We help investors to manage and understand their investments; but we don't ask and store any information about your brokerage account. We provide simple tools to help you import and export your portfolios so that you can easily create and manage your accounts. By using any of the Services, you consent to the terms of this Policy. 

Policy Effective Date: May 25th 2018

This privacy policy sets out how Macroaxis LLC uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this service. Macroaxis is fully committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Please note that Macroaxis LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page once in a while to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

This policy is effective from May 25th 2018

## Personally Identifiable Information

Registration on Macroaxis is strictly voluntary. You do get some cool information and access to certain great features if you do register, but membership is not necessary to get the public information available on site. Macroaxis collects personally identifiable information that you provide to us. This includes (at your discretion) your **name** , an **email address** and an **organization**. Our software uses this information to personalize and manage the Macroaxis website for you. 

Information| When Deleted  
---|---  
First Name| 36 months after last login or upon request  
Last Name| 36 months after last login or upon request  
Email Address| 36 months after last login or upon request  
Organization| 36 months after last login or upon request  
  
## We'll Keep You In Touch

When you choose to register with us, Macroaxis logs you in automatically using your email address. This makes it easier for you as you don't have to create and remember a login identifier. The use of your email address for login also allows Macroaxis the chance to email you a new password in case you forget or lost your old one. 

Macroaxis gives you the option of receiving emails from us. We'll keep you in loop about new features available on our service. We notify our users only for big release so you will not get more than 1 email in every quarter. If you like, you can opt out any time. Our emails are sent from a Macroaxis address and are sent to your real email address. Every email that we send has an instruction how to opt out from our notifications, so you can be unsubscribed when you want. We do hate spam and suspect that you do too. 

## Investment Accounts and Brokerage Aggregation

Macroaxis may use Plaid Technologies, Inc. ('Plaid') to verify your investment account and confirm your portfolio positions and balance prior to approving an import. Macroaxis only shares your information with Plaid in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information shared with Plaid is treated by Plaid in accordance with its Privacy Policy, available at [https://plaid.com/legal/](https://plaid.com/legal/#end-user-privacy-policy "Plaid Privacy Policy"). 

## Absolutely No Sharing

What's yours is yours. "You Info" that you chose to share with us is not going anywhere off of our site. We won't sell your info to anyone. There might be one exception in the event Macroaxis itself is sold. In this case we would transfer your info to our buyers so that they could continue to provide the same great service. Please note, you can always change your provided information in the "Profile" page on Macroaxis. 

## How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to help you evaluate our service, and enhance our software functionality. We may also use your personal information a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, and analytics. Macroaxis also stores, processes, and maintains Personal Information related to you in order to provide client support, offer new products or services. As a User, you may choose not to provide such information to us, but if you choose not to provide such information, you will not be able to become a Client. 

## How We Protect Your Information

Security is our top priority. We take every precaution intended to keep the information stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Should any data breaches become known to us, we will notify responsible authorities as soon as possible, including technical details of the breach as well as extend of personal data affected. In addition, if the stolen data contains unencrypted personal data, we will inform you as soon as possible. Your personal information is held on the servers operated by Amazon Web Services, Inc and is physically located in the United States of America. 

## Browser Cookies

When you visit Macroaxis we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more 'cookies'. Your browser will store these cookies on you computer in a small text file. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better service, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. You can enable your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may disable access to some services and tools that we offer. 

Cookie| Used By| Used For| Expiration  
---|---|---|---  
maxis| macroaxis.com| Faster sign on using 'remember me' feature| 3 months  
maxisBmk| macroaxis.com| Remember user selected benchmark| 3 months  
maxisCty| macroaxis.com| Remember user selected country| 3 months  
maxisCry| macroaxis.com| Remember user selected currency| 3 months  
_x_w| support.macroaxis.com| Freshdesk Support| When Session Ends  
_helpkit_session| support.macroaxis.com| Freshdesk Support| When Session Ends  
ticket_view_choice| support.macroaxis.com| Freshdesk Support| 26 months  
__stripe_mid| macroaxis.com| Stripe Payment Gateway| 22 months  
  
You can find more details on our cookie policy page 

## Age Matters

Macroaxis does not knowingly collect information from people under the age of 18. If we become aware of the fact that a minor is attempting to submit this information, we will inform the minor that he or she is ineligible to do so. We will then remove this information from our records. 

## Change is Life

Macroaxis reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If there are material changes to this statement on how Macroaxis will use your information, we will prominently post these changes prior to implementing them. If you use our website after we post these changes, this indicates your acceptance of them. Regardless of later updates, we will follow the privacy practices described in this privacy statement at the time you provided us with your information. If you have questions about our privacy policies, please  send feedback.
